<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="open_helper_classname">ORMDatabaseHelper</string>

    <string name="contact_phone">Phone: +234 (0) 803 794 9311</string>
    <string name="contact_email">Email: support@dmas-nig.com</string>
    <string name="copyright">copyright 2014 DMAS</string>
    <string name="dialog_text">Are you sure of this ?</string>

    <string name="dialog_no">No</string>
    <string name="dialog_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_close">close</string>

    <string name="developer">Developed by UDcreate \n <u>www.udonline.net</u></string>

    <string name="account_active">Loading...</string>
    <string name="account_inactive">Loading...</string>
    <string name="last_subscribed">Last Subscription: Loading...</string>
    <string name="sub_type">Subscription type: Loading...</string>
    <string name="sub_exp">Expires: Loading...</string>
    <string name="subscribe_hint">Enter your pin</string>
    <string name="btn_subscribe">Subscribe me</string>

    <string name="app_name">DMAS</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="username">Nkwocha Udoka</string>
    <string name="useremail">hello@udonline.net</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="accept_terms">By creating an account, you are agreeing with our terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="startup_register">Register</string>
    <string name="startup_signin">Sign in</string>
    <string name="startup_welcome">Divine Mercy App</string>
    <string name="login_login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_fpswd">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="register_fname">Fullname</string>
    <string name="register_signup">Signup</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_websearch">Web search</string>
    <string name="app_not_available">Sorry, there\'s no web browser available</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="action_refresh">refresh</string>

    <string name="close_btn">close</string>
    <string name="testimony_hint">type your testimony</string>

    <string name="item_price">Price: 3,000</string>

    <string name="prayer_by_three">
        You expired, Jesus, but the source of life gushed
forth for souls
and the ocean of mercy opened up for the
whole world.\n \n
O Fountain of Life, unfathomable Divine Mercy, \n
envelop the whole world and empty Yourself out \n
upon us.\n \n
O Blood and Water, \n
which gushed forth from the Heart of Jesus \n
as a fountain of mercy for us,\n
I trust in You.\n \n

Holy God, Holy Mighty One, Holy Immortal One, \n
Have mercy on us and on the whole world. (3times) \n
JESUS, King of mercy, I trust in You! \n
Amen \n \n

*Note: In the official R. Catholic version, the last
stanza should hasBeenRead as follows: \n
"O Blood and Water which flowed out from the
heart of Jesus \n
as a Fountain of Mercy for us, I trust in You!.
(3x) \n \n
Jesus, I Trust in You." \n
Amen.
    </string>

    <string name="about_divine_mercy_content">
        The message of Divine Mercy was given to a
Polish nun named Sister Faustina. It was
revealed to her by Jesus in a private revelation
that is fully approved by the Church. The
message of Divine Mercy is not something that is
new or additional to the Gospel message. \n
In fact, it is the same core message presented in a
particular way with a few new devotions. This
novena is one of those devotions. \n
St. Faustina reports in her diary that she
transcribed the words of the novena as Jesus
dictated them to her day-by-day beginning on
Good Friday. \n
While this novena can be prayed any time, it is
fitting that this novena begins on the day that
Jesus gave us His Life. Good Friday is the perfect
time to begin meditating on the Mercy of God
towards us who need His mercy so much. \n
We end the novena on the eve of the Feast of
Mercy, a feast day established by Pope John
Paul II in response to St. Faustina’s revelation.
This is a very important feast and the novena is
an important part of our preparation for the
Feast of Mercy, Divine Mercy Sunday. \n
“The Lord told me to say this chaplet for nine
days before the Feast of Mercy.  \n
 It is to begin on Good Friday. ‘By this novena, I will grant every
possible grace to souls.’”  (Diary 796) \n
On April 30th, 2000 Pope John Paul II instituted
Divine Mercy Sunday as an official feast of the
Church. In doing this he said, “by this act today,
I pass on the message of Divine Mercy to the
new millennium. I pass it on because I want
people to know the better face of God, and that
of his Divine Mercy, and through it, the better
face of their brethren. The light of the message
of Divine Mercy which the Lord wished to renew
in the world, will be as much a beacon of hope
for the third millennium, as the apostles were in
the first.” \n
This is clearly a very important and powerful
devotion. \n
<strong>Purpose of the Devotion</strong>  \n
You can pray the Divine Mercy Novena for any
reason you want. God’s Mercy is relevant and
effective in all parts of our lives. However, there
are some specific reasons you may want to call
on the Divine Mercy in your prayer life. \n
For the dying \n
For Poland \n
For forgiveness and mercy \n
For conversion \n
For healing \n
In preparation for Divine Mercy Sunday
So, let us join together and beg for God’s Divine
Mercy together through this Divine Mercy
Novena!
    </string>

    <string name="pray_title">
        Prayer To St. Faustina
    </string>

    <string name="prayer_to_st_faustina">
        O Jesus, who filled Saint Faustina with profound veneration for the boundless mercy,\n
        deign, if it be, Your holy will, to grant me through her intercession,\n
        the grace for which I fervently pray… May sins render me unworthy for Your mercy,\n
        but be mindful of St. Faustina’s sacrifice and self-denial,\n
        and reward her virtues by granting the petition, which, with childlike trust,\n
        I present, to You through her intercession.
    </string>

    <string name="concluding_prayer">
        Concluding Prayer \n \n
        I fly to Your Mercy, Compassionate God, Who alone are good.
        Although my misery is great and my offences are many,
        I trust in Your Mercy because You are the God of Mercy,
        and it has never been heard of in all ages,
        nor do Heaven or Earth remember,
        that a soul trusting in Your Mercy has been disappointed. (State your intentions)

        \n \n

      Jesus, Friend of a lonely heart, You are my haven.
        You are my peace. You are my salvation. \n
        You are my serenity in moments of struggle and amidst an ocean of doubts. \n
        Amen
    </string>

    <string name="for_the_sake_prayer">
        For the sake of His sorrowful passion, \n
have mercy on us and on the \n
whole world.\n
    </string>

    <string name="closing_prayer">
        I fly to Your Mercy, Compassionate God, Who alone are good. Although my misery is great and my offences are many, I trust in Your Mercy because You are the God of Mercy, and it has never been heard of in all ages, nor do Heaven or Earth remember, that a soul trusting in Your Mercy has been disappointed. (State your intentions)
\n
Jesus, Friend of a lonely heart, You are my haven. You are my peace. You are my salvation. You are my serenity in moments of struggle and amidst an ocean of doubts. Amen
    </string>

    <string name="from_diary">
        From the Diary of St. Faustina
    </string>

    <string name="title_prayer">
        Title of the prayer
    </string>

</resources>
